well thank you very much it's an honor
to have President zalinski of Ukraine
and we've been working very hard very
close and we've actually known each
other for a long time we've been dealing
with each other for a long time and very
well uh we had little negotiation spat
but that worked out great I think for
for both countries I think for the world
actually Beyond both countries and we
have something that is a very fair deal
and we look forward to getting in and
digging digging digging and working and
getting some of the rare earth but it
means we're going to be inside and it's
uh it's a big commitment from the United
States and we appreciate working with
you very much and uh we will continue to
do that we have had some very good
discussions with Russia I spoke with
President Putin and we're going to try
and bring this to a close it's something
that you want and that he wants we have
to negotiate a deal but we've started
the confines of a deal and I think
something can happen uh the big thing is
the uh number of soldiers mostly at this
point but soldiers being killed you're
losing thousands of soldiers on both
sides we're losing a lot of soldiers and
we want to see it stop and we want to
see the money get put to different kinds
of use like rebuilding the rebuilding
and we're going to be working very hard
but we've had a lot of very good
conversations I will say until we came
along the Biden Administration didn't
speak to Russia whatsoever they didn't
speak to anybody they just allowed this
to
continue and uh I will say that uh I'll
say in front of you you've heard me say
it a thousand times if I were president
of this war would have never happened we
would have had a deal negotiated for you
without having to go through what you've
gone through but you uh your soldiers
have been unbelievably Brave we've given
them great equipment but they somebody
has to use the equipment they've been
unbelievably Brave and we give him great
credit this was supposed to be over very
quickly and uh here we are three years
later so I give tremendous credit to
your generals and your soldiers and
yourself in the sense that uh it's been
very hard fighting very tough fighting
they great Fighters and uh you have to
be very proud of them from that stand
but now we want to get it over with it's
enough right if we want to get it over
with so uh it's enough honor to have you
here thank you very much for coming
we're going to sign uh the agreement at
the conference in the East room in a
little while right after lunch and we'll
be having lunch together we're also
discussing some other things and we
appreciate everybody being here it's a
somewhat of an exciting moment but the
really exciting moment is where we get a
when they stop the shooting or we end up
with a deal and I think we're fairly
close to getting that and uh an honor to
have you and please please like to say
something yeah thank you so much Mr
President thank you for invitation and
uh really I hope that this um document
first document will be first step to
real security guarantees for Ukraine our
people our children I really count on it
and of course we count that America will
not stop support really for us is very
important to support and to continue it
I want to discuss it with details
further during our ation and of course
the infrastructure or security
guarantees because for today I
understand what Europe is ready to do
and of course I want to discuss with you
what United States will be ready to do
and uh I really count on your strong
position to stop Putin and uh and you
said that enough with the War I think
that is very important Ben to say these
wars to Putin at the very beginning at
the very beginning of War because he is
a killer and terrorist but I hope that
together we can stop him but for us it's
very important to you know to save our
country our values our freedom the
democracy and of course uh no
compromises with the killer about our
territories but it will be later and of
course I what I wanted you know we spoke
about it by phone with you about the
Dron production we have very good Dron
production I think the best one in the
world for today because of the war yes
and uh of course we need need very much
uh the air defense you have the best air
defense in the world and really you
helped us under attacks of Russians and
I want to speak how we can exchange the
licenses we're open to share the
licenses of all our drones with you of
course with the United States and we
need licenses for quick production of
air defense even after the war we need
our nation to be come that we're secured
so that's why we need this air shield
and of course about this uh I want to
speak about the contingence I think that
France and UK already spoke to you and
we know that Europe is ready but without
the United States they will not be ready
to be as strong as we need and uh the
last point last not least uh about
exchange about our people and children
and you know that this crazy Russian
that they stolen 20,000 of children
Ukrainian children they changed their
names they changed
their you know their families relatives
and uh now they in Russia we want to
bring them back and really it's a big
big dream task and goal for me and and
the our Warriors we by the way Mr we
brought we exchanged we yes released
more than 4,000 Warriors from Russian
prison but there are
thousands more in the prison I wanted to
share with you some some images how how
it's
just just can can I can I now yeah pleas
some minute one minute one minute I just
you to understand what in what
circumstances in what situation they are
and what the attitude of Russia to our
prisons that guys just you before before
and
after and you see before and after just
you to understand now thousands of such
guys ladies and men there and that so
they don't eat they beat them and they
you know they do a lot of a lot of you
know bad things so out out of even
during the war There Are Rules everybody
knows There are rules during the war
these guys they don't have any rules you
see that 50 60 kilg left and and a lot
of such things and I didn't want to show
you what what the changes with images of
children because I will share just share
with you and I'm I mean it's
looking tragic Y and tough stuff yeah I
wanted very much to to give you and you
you see this is Pastor by the way they
stolen pastors because it's not Russian
Church they stolen pastors and move
pastors to the prison we at the end of
last year we we brought three pastors
and we we could exchange them and this
is Pastor is
see yeah that's tough yeah so I mean
this I wanted to show you and um this so
thank you very much we want to get that
ended right yeah yeah of course of
course we will I think we will I think
we will and uh we have to of course do
you have any questions
please thank you Mr President um with
the how much money is the US going to
put into the fund that that is being
created today and how does this provide
long-term security for Ukraine well we
don't know exactly how much because
we're going to be putting some money in
a fun
uh that we're going to get from the raar
earth that we're going to be taking and
sharing in terms of Revenue so it's
going to be a lot of money will be made
from the sale and from the use of raw
Earth and as you know our country
doesn't have much raw Earth we have a
lot of oil and gas but we don't have a
lot of the raw Earth and what we do have
is protected by the environmentalists
but that could be unprotected but still
it's not very much uh they have F among
the best in the world in terms of R so
we're going to be using that taking it
using it for all of the things we do
including Ai and including weapons and
the military and it's uh really going to
very much satisfy our needs so something
that just worked out uh really well we
have a lot of oil and we have a lot of
gas we have a lot but we don't have raw
Earth so uh this uh this has just about
every component of the raw Earth that we
need for computers for all of the things
we do this puts us in great shape and
longterm security for UK do this
provided I think they're going to have
great long I think once we make the
agreement that's going to be 95% of it
it's they're not going to go back to
fighting uh I've spoken with President
Putin and uh I think I mean I feel very
strong I've known them for a long time
and I feel very strongly that uh they're
very serious about it and we'll make a
deal and when the deal is made I don't
think we talk about security everyone's
talking about the other day all they
talked about was security I said let me
make the deal first I have to make the
deal first I don't worry about security
right now I got have to we have to have
a deal cuz right now last week 2,000
soldiers died on both sides 2,000 and
they're losing a th000 2,000 3,000 a
week so as we sit here and we talk
people are getting shot and dying on the
battlefield and you know they're not
American soldiers but they're Russian
soldiers and they're Ukrainian soldiers
and we want to be able to stop it and
want to be able also to spend money on
other things we don't want to this is a
tremendous amount of money and what the
Biden Administration did was terrible
they were giving money but he had no
security on the money Europe as you know
gave much less money but they had
security it was in the form of a loan
they get their money back and we didn't
and now at least we're protected because
the American taxpayer has to be
protected too but uh this is an
incredible agreement for Ukraine because
we have a big investment in their
country now and and what what they have
very few people have and we're able to
uh really go forward with very very
high-tech things and many other things
including Weaponry Weaponry that we're
going to use in many locations but that
we need for our country this allows this
allows us to do this will you continue
will you I'm sorry I'm
sorry yes go ahead please if I can just
add yes in the document there is one of
the very important points uh if we speak
about business and investment we never
had LG terminals in Ukraine this
document will open I mean the next
documents but anyway the here we see in
the framework we we see we see a really
good will for this LG terminals for us
is very important and I think for
security of European continent we have
the biggest storage gas storage we have
the biggest in Europe yes it's
yeah and we can use it you get for LNG
use it for L and we will do it and
really we we can help Europe because
Europe really helped president Trump
said that they made uh less support but
they have our friends and they our very
supportive uh Partners they really gave
a lot Mr BR they really they did they
gave a lot but they gave much less no
much less no no don't argue with no okay
okay yeah please uh Mr President Trump
you have repeatedly called the deal with
Ukraine has as a historical one and as a
president of the United States you make
historical decision in other issues
which affect America and other world so
uh what place in the world history do
you want to take
and do you associate your yourself with
any famous historical
figures yeah I'd say George Washington
Abraham Lincoln I would say I'm far
superior to George Washington and
Abraham Lincoln now you know I'm only
kidding right because when I say that
the fake news is going to go wild
they're going to say he considers
himself to be better than Washington but
you never know you never know uh I don't
compare myself to any I just have I'm
here to do a job we've had a great 35
days or whatever it might be a month a
little more than a month uh We've
accomplished tremendous amounts not only
this this would be a very great
achievement if we could get this the war
stopped and get them back to
normalization I think that's going to
happen we've had very good talks on both
sides as you know but uh I think we've
done a very good job just generally if
you look at all of the things we've done
in 30 days they're saying there's never
been a a opening for a president the
first month uh there's never been a
first month like uh like we've had and
this is one of the very important things
this to me is one of the most important
things
because we have tremendous death taking
place as we speak and I don't want to
have that you know think of the parents
think of the whether they're in Russia
or Ukraine think of the parents of all
these people being killed needlessly
they came to all should have never
started this would if I were president
this would have never started
Mr Mr will you continue sending military
aid to Ukraine after you uh the US signs
this agreement with
Ukraine zensky do you feel like the US
is on your side that the president that
President Trump is on your side at this
uh at this
moment what do you think he wants to
know do you think that sort of a stupid
question because I guess I guess we
wouldn't be here if I
wasn't but uh I think that I think that
the United States on our side from the
very beginning of
occupation and uh I think that President
Trump on our side and and of course I
not I'm sure that United States
President will not stop support this is
crucial for us it's important for us yes
and Putin president speaks about the
people and the soldiers which are dying
but they came to our territory they came
to our land they began this war and they
have to stop and uh I think all this is
the question with really the most
important question can president Trump I
hope yes with some other allies to stop
Putin withdraw these enemies our ene
withdraw these troops from our land and
I think that you asked about the history
about the I think that if president or
when he will stop Putin if president
Trump will bring peace to our country I
think he will be on this wall time we've
had very very good uh
talks what about minitary a to Ukraine
president m m president zinski just said
that there' be no compromises with uh um
Vladimir Putin um I just wanted to ask
both of you firstly um are there
compromises that you think that
president zinski is going to have to
make and president zilinski is there
anything that you might you think that
you may be able to offer or bring to the
table for example elections thank you I
think you're going to have to always
make compromises you can't do any deals
without compromises so certainly he's
going to have to make some compromises
but hopefully they won't be as big as
some people think you're going to have
to make that's all it's all we can do
I'm here as a as an arbitrator as a
mediator to a certain extent between two
parties that have uh been very hostile
to put it mildly they've been very
hostile this has been a vicious War this
been a vicious War you know it's a very
level Battlefield and uh those bullets
go out and as I've said many times we're
talking about it with Pete uh many times
the only thing stopping those bullets is
a human body and in the case we're
talking about generally young human
bodies are stopping a lot of bullets
it's dead level that's what why it's
great Farmland it's great land it's
great Farmland but there's very little
protection against the bullets that are
being and other things that are being
shot so all I can do is see if I can get
everybody at the table and get an
agreement and I think we're going to end
up with an agreement otherwise I
wouldn't probably be even here
today I Mr President I got two questions
for you think ultimately your legacy
will be The Peacemaker and not the
president that led this country into
another war and ended Foreign Wars and
I've got I hope it will I mean I hope
I'm going to
be uh remembered as a
peacemaker uh this is this would be a
great thing if we could do this I'm
doing this to save lives more than
anything else second is to save a lot of
money but I considered that to be far
less important uh so I hope I'm going to
thank you Brian for that question it was
a nice question uh I hope I'll be known
and recognized as a peacemaker this this
would be a great thing to solve this is
a very dangerous situation you know this
could lead to a third world war this is
this was headed in the wrong direction
if this election were lost if we didn't
win this election and by way we won it
by a lot that was a mandate we won every
swing state we won the popular vote by
millions and millions of votes we won
everything uh the districts you look at
the areas of of red take a look at a map
this was a big mandate and uh this was
one of the things I said we're going to
get this thing settled if we didn't win
I think this would have this could have
very well ended up in a third world war
and that would not that would not have
been a good situation what was your
second question my second question for
president Smith zinski do you ever why
don't you wear a
suit wear a suit you're the highest
level in this country's office and you
refuse to wear a suit just want to you
own a suit yeah you have problems I a
lot of Americans have problems with you
not resp I don't
have uh I will wear costume after this
war will finish okay yes
maybe one maybe something like yours yes
maybe some something better I I don't
know we will see maybe something cheaper
than yeah thank
[Music]
you Mr President are you going to send
more arms to Ukraine in case there's no
peace yeah we're going to have arms to
Ukraine yeah sure hopefully I won't have
to send very much because hopefully
we're going to have it finished we're
looking forward to finish in this
quickly uh we're not looking forward to
sending a lot of arms we're looking
forward to getting the war finished so
we can uh do other things but uh we very
much appreciate the agreement because we
needed what they had and we're treating
you know our country is now treated
fairly Biden didn't do that Biden didn't
he didn't know what the hell he was
doing this should have never happened
this should have never started but uh
you know sure the answer is yes but
hopefully we won't have to send much
because I'm looking forward to get it
done getting it done quickly very
quickly does that provide security
guarantees Mr President uh I don't want
to talk about security yet because I
want to get the deal done you know you
fall into the same trap like everybody
else a million times you said over and
over I want to get the deal done
security is so easy that's about 2% of
the problem uh I'm not worried about
security I'm worried about getting the
deal done uh the security is the easy
part security is very nice everybody
stops shooting and now will Europe put
people there I know France is going to I
know the UK is going to I know other
countries are going to and they happen
to be right next or we haven't committed
but we could conceivably you know we
have Security in a different form we'll
have workers there uh digging digging
digging taking the raw Earth so that we
can create a lot of great product in
this country uh so in that sense you
have something but we haven't determined
that yet I will say uh in speaking to
France and in speaking to and they were
here as you know last week and just the
other day uh they have committed to a
lot of security I don't think you're
going to need much security I think once
this deal gets done it's over Russia is
not going to want to go back and
nobody's going to want to go back when
this when this deal ends I really
believe this deal is is going to be over
uh question yeah please go ahead go
ahead thank you so president thank
youing here starm at the White House
this past week both of appraised your
courage and conviction to lead the
pathway towards peace yes part of that
involved though re-engaging Russia in
diplomatic relations something that
previous leaders lacked the conviction
to do so what gave you the moral courage
and conviction to step forward and Lead
that well I love this guy who are you
with one American News sir well that's
why I like him one American News does a
great job that's very I like the
question I think it's a very good
question it is it's a pathway to peace
it's a pathway to getting something s
and I feel that as the head of this
country I have an obligation to do that
plus you know we're very much involved
we got involved uh it's too bad we got
involved because there should have been
no involvement because there should have
been no war and there shouldn't have
been October 7th that would have never
happened as you know Iran was broke they
had no money to give to Hezbollah they
had no money to give to Hamas they would
Stone Cold broke and then under Biden
they became rich as hell they went from
no money to $300
billion in a period of four years and
they gave a lot of that money away and
you see what happened and that's a real
mess also that we hope to be able to
solve but uh no I I appreciate your
question very much I just I feel I have
an obligation to try and uh do something
to stop the
death if I can if I can answer yes if I
can answer sorry please please and I do
like your clothing though yeah really I
have to I think he's a great guy by the
way but I I don't know if you two like
each other but you know what I think
he's just I think he's this guy I don't
know I think he's just beautiful so I
have more I have more serious things
than answer on such question I will
answer on more serious question if I can
yeah so please uh about security
guarantees and about just fire we can't
just speak about this fire and speak and
speak it will not work just this fire
will not never work
because I'm like a president I have I
have this experience and not only me
Ukraine before before my presidency from
the 2014 Putin broken 25 times 25 times
he
broken his own signature 25 times he
broken C fire he never broke to me he
never broke no no he was the president
the president never broke in 2016 you
been the president Mr Mr President
you've been the president but he for he
had of course not with you but he had
during those period he had conversations
with our side and we had Normandy for
format you know the France Germany
Ukraine and Russia and he broken 25
times that's why we will
never accept just ceire it will not work
without security guarantees security
guarantees maybe president is right
about this document and other but this
document is not enough strong Army is
enough because he soldiers afraid Putin
soldiers afraid of our soldiers when
we're strong enough if we are not strong
enough if we are empty if our stor is
empty we can't defend our our land today
you know he knows that we have me all
the world knows that we have meeting yes
why he's using ballistic Putin today
using ballistic on our Hospital schools
and Etc ballistic so he knows that we
are here and that President Trump is
really have good will to stop to stop
this war
and I and you you hear now the president
so why he's using so he doesn't want to
stop he doesn't want but I hope that we
will do it really we'll do it security
when we speak about security guarantees
when the Europeans are ready for
contingence they need USA back stop if
there will not be United States we will
not never have any contigent strong
cones from the Europeans because they
don't want to divide airines connection
between the United States the main and
strongest C and Europeans and this is
crucial this is important that what we
want to speak about very much this is
very important and a
defense so air defense really we have
big deficit with all these systems and
we need to provide this we need it very
much otherwise Putin will never stop and
we'll go further and further he doesn't
want he he hate us you know it's not
about me he hate Ukrainian
he thinks that we are not a nation he
thinks and he shared This Ss I think
maybe with your team also I don't know
but with all the Europeans in media
officially and not he always said that
we there is no such country such Nation
such language and such life like
Ukrainian no he really doesn't respect
all the ukrainians and he wants destroy
us we we and you are right Mr President
that's 2%
this document maybe other documents it's
a very good Star very good but it will
not enough to stop this
person Mr President may I one more
question please yeah I I
ask question this is the rule this is
Rule of the war this is the rule of the
war during all the centuries all the
history this is the rule of the war who
began those pay this is the rule Putin
began this war he has to pay all money
for renovation he has to pay of course
some Russian assets what we have in
Europe about 300 billions we can use
them we can use for Innovation and buy
military support from the United States
also we can do it but it's not enough
it's not I this question that you didn't
like because I wanted to know go ahead
please wait one second I want I ask this
question that you didn't like because I
want to know if you want to position
yourself in the middle between Russia
and Ukraine or on the Ukraine side I'm
in the middle I want to solve this thing
I'm for I'm for both I want to get it
solved and uh it's wonderful to speak
badly about somebody else but uh I want
to get it solved if we can solve it
great if we can't solve it they're going
to have to fight it out and who knows
what's going to happen but I want to see
it get solved follow up one more
question about US troops in Europe uh
after Russian invasion of Ukraine uh
your creditor sent additional troops to
Eastern Europe including Poland my
country yeah are you committed to
keeping this troops on the Eastern flank
of
NATO uh in the future I'm very committed
to Poland I think Poland is really
stepped up and done a great job for NATO
they as you know they paid more than
they had to they are one of the finest
groups of people I've ever known uh I'm
very committed to Poland what about Bal
Poland's in a tough neighborhood you
know what about Baltic the baltics uh
the baltics uh they got a lot of it's a
tough neighborhood too but we're
committed we're going to be very
committed and we're committed to Nato
but NATO has to step up and the
Europeans have to step up more than they
have and I want to see them equalize
because they are in for far less than
we're in and they should be at least
equal you understand that why is the
United States we have an ocean in
between why is the United States in for
so much more money and other things as
Europe with that being said and as you
said they've also been obviously very
helpful but we have put in far more than
they have and I think they should
equalize yeah please go ahead today what
changed between the first time that
secretary Bess gave president zinsky the
agreement and today for
we made a deal so Wasing Factor I'm I'm
a business person we made a deal that's
what
changed I didn't think we were going to
make a deal and uh we ended up making
the deal so that Chang Mr President what
and how do you envision a trilateral
summit with president zinsky and I don't
know but it's well they don't like each
other I can tell you that okay they do
not like each other this is not a love
match and it's unfortunate that's why
you're in this situation Mr the United
States should not have allowed this to
happen Okay the United
States run by a man that didn't know
much I'm going to be very nice run by an
incompetent person very incompetent
person should never have allowed this to
happen I've stopped Wars I've stopped
many wars my people will tell you I
stopped Wars that nobody ever heard
about I sto Wars before they ever
started you can look at some of uh some
I could give you a lot of Nations that
would tell you right now they were
probably going to war I could tell you
right now there's a nation thinking
about going to war on something that
nobody in this room has ever even heard
about two smaller Nations but big still
big and i' I think I've stopped it but
this should have never happened Mr
President about uh sorry just a second
uh about the any negotiations that first
of all I want I want really to tell you
and I think that everybody understand
that Ukraine more than ukrainians nobody
wants to stop this war but at the future
any negotiations it's understandable
that two uh sides of the war not Russia
and the United States because this is
not the war between Russia and the
United States This Is War of Russia
against Ukraine and Ukrainian people so
these two sides will be at the any
anyway will be at the negotiation a
negotiation table then of course of
course United States like the strongest
partner of the Ukraine and of course
Europe I think Europe is very important
I want to speak about it with the
president yes Europe is very important
for us because we really defend Europe
for today all Europeans are really
recognized that we are defending line
and they have real life and our people
are dying that's why they helped us and
also it's about the NAT yes between like
the president said you have big nice
ocean yes between us but if we will not
stay Russia will go further to baltics
and to Poland by the way but first to
the baltics it's understandable for them
because they've been they've been in the
USSR you know they they've been one of
the republics of the USSR and Putin
wants to bring them back to his Empire
it's a fact and when he will go there if
we will not stay you will fight you're
American soldiers it doesn't matter do
you have Ocean or not your soldiers will
fight Mr President would are you willing
to visit Ukraine for Odessa which is
known to be ax it was my question yeah
sorry I don't want to talk about Odessa
now let's not talk about Odessa I want
to talk about making a deal getting
peace we don't have to talk about Odessa
but a lot of cities have been destroyed
a lot of cities that are not recognized
able there's not a building standing and
a lot of a lot of things Mr you have to
come and to look no no no we have very
good cities yes a lot of things been
destroyed but mostly cities alive and
people work and children go to school
sometimes it's very difficult sometimes
closer to Front Line children have to go
to underground schools or online but we
live Ukraine is fighting and Ukraine
lives this is very important and maybe
puting is sharing this information that
he destroyed us no he lost
700,000 people 700,000 soldiers you lost
ever SE yes Mr President you
ask Mr thank you president um when did
you last speak with President Putin and
what did he say that couple of days ago
and what what did he tell you that gave
you the assurance that he wanted peace
well that's what I do my whole life is
deals I know pretty good uh and I really
I've uh I've known him for a long time
I've dealt with him for a long time he
had to suffer through the uh Russia hoax
you know Russia Russia Russia was a hoax
it was all Biden it was nothing to do
with him so he had to suffer through
that and he he was able to do that uh I
think that uh he wants to make a deal
and he like to see it end it's all I do
that's what I do my whole life that's
what I do is make deals and I'm in the
middle of a mess because this is a real
mess it's a very dangerous one if this
doesn't get solved now it's not going to
get solved for a long time so I hope
we're going to I hope we're going to get
it solved in the back please thank you
Mr President uh prime minister Storer
claimed repeatedly that his government
believes in free speech and was not
engaged in censorship uh but his
country's government arrest people for
memes and thought crimes and even more
worrisome is pressuring uh American
companies to to to censor Americans on
his behalf um how can he be a reliable
trustworthy partner when he says are
demonstrably false on such an important
topic well we actually spoke to them
about that yesterday and we thought they
took it very very much too far JD was
very strong on it so was I and so was
Marco and we've been speaking to him
about it Marco would you like to say
something about that we we have concerns
obviously with the conduct of
particularly as it impacts Americans and
there's real concern that American
speech which is online could fall into
the hands of British or any country's
jurisdiction and so this is a point that
vice president made at Munich and and I
think it's a very compelling one that
what unites us with Europe as much as
anything else is these shared values and
one of them being free speech and so
Americans are threatened by it we're
going to need to take action in that
regard it's AIG it's actually a very
important question we we spoke about
this in detail with the Prime Minister
and the Ford secretary and others at at
lunch yesterday and I know that
Secretary of Commerce lutnick followed
up in private meetings last night this
is really important We Believe Americans
have the right to speak their mind even
if we in this room disagree with them
they have the right to speak their mind
in the Public Square which is often
online these days and we're going to
defend that right as it pertains to
American companies and American citizens
vigorously if we have to I do think that
under the president's leadership we're
going to find common ground with our
friends in the UK on this question but
it remains to be seen the principle that
will guide us is we believe in free
speech in this country and we'll fight
for it for American citizens Mr Mr
President the deal is there any other
oil and gas component to the deal is it
all critical a little bit we'll see on L
but we're not really looking for that so
much we got a lot we have more than
anybody in the world by far so no we're
not talking about it too much but a
little bit I think it it it affects also
but for the most part no and Sir is
there any uh agreement from uh Ukraine
to purchase uh us LG as part of the deal
or is that on the table at all no Mr
pres we don't need Mr President I just
wanted to ask you about
you just mentioned that you'd spoken to
Vladimir Putin a couple of days ago just
to be clear that's a new call not the
one that you I've spoken to him on
numerous occasions okay and how was the
latest call and what did you
discuss how did it go are you serious
with that question I am I'd love to know
it went well I think I think we're going
to have a deal on the minerals deal Mr
President some of those minerals are in
the east of Ukraine not far from the
front lines and in areas that Russ very
good question thank you so much
President Putin to to withdraw his
forces from those areas if you're
there's us well we'll take a look at at
the time we have a lot of area uh it's a
very big area we're talking about so
we'll take a look I'll study that and
I'll see and who would protect those
minerals if if they are us interest
would that be Ukraine they'll be
protected the agreement will protect him
the agreement yeah we're signing an
agreement what if Russia tries to invade
or or there's Russian agression spot I
just told you I don't think that's going
to happen and if that were going to
happen I wouldn't make a deal if I
thought that was going to happen I
wouldn't make a deal some people you
know they ought to focus on CNN on
Survival not asking me these ridiculous
questions focus on Surviving because
CNN's got such low ratings I don't think
they're going to survive uh let's go
yeah please go ahead more since already
I already mentioned Poland uh Poland was
under Russian control for decades after
the second world war when I was a kid I
looked at the United States not only as
a most powerful country richest country
in the world the country that has great
music great movies great muscle cars but
also as a Force for good do you and now
I'm talking with my friends in Poland
and they they are worried that you align
yourself too much with
Putin what's your message for
them well if I didn't align myself with
both of them you'd never have a deal you
want me to say uh really terrible things
about Putin and then say hi Vladimir how
are we doing on the deal that doesn't
work that way I'm not aligned with Putin
I'm not aligned with anybody I'm aligned
with the United States of America and
for the good of the world I'm aligned
with the world and I want to get this
thing over with you see the hatred he's
got for Putin it's very tough for me to
make a deal with that kind of hat he's
got tremendous hatred and I understand
that but I can tell you the other side
isn't exactly in love with you know him
either
uh so it's not a question of alignment I
have to I'm aligned with the world I
want to get the things set i'm aligned
with
Europe I want to see if we can get this
thing done you want me to be tough I
could be tougher than any human being
you've ever seen I'd be so tough but
you're never going to get a deal that
way so that's the way it goes all right
one more question yeah please I would
respond to this so look for four years
in the United States of America we had a
president who stood up at press
conferences and talked tough about
Vladimir Putin and then Putin invaded
Ukraine and destroyed a significant
chunk of the country the path to peace
and the path to Prosperity is maybe
engaging in diplomacy we tried the
pathway of Joe Biden of thumping our
chest and pretending that the president
of the United States's words mattered
more than the president of the United
States's actions what makes America a
good country is America engaging in
diplomacy that's what president Trump is
doing can I ask you sure yeah yeah okay
so he occupied it uh our parts big parts
of Ukraine part of East and Crimea uh so
he occupied it on
so during a lot of years so I'm not
speaking about just Biden but those time
was Obama then President Obama then
president Trump then President Biden now
the president Trump and God bless that's
now president Trump will stop him but
during 2014 nobody stopped him he just
occupied and took he killed people you
know what the contact
2015 2014 2014 2014 yeah so I was not
here yeah buta right yes but during 2014
till
2022 you the what the situation the same
the people have been dying on the
contact line nobody stopped him you know
that we had con ation with him a lot of
conversation my bilateral conversation
and we signed with him me like a new
president in 2019 I signed with him the
deal I signed with him macron and Merkel
we signed ceasefire ceasefire all of
them told me that he will never go we
signed him gas contract gas contract yes
but after that he broken this seire he
killed our people and he didn't exchange
prisoners we signed the exchange of
prisoners but he didn't do it what kind
of diplomacy JD you are speaking about
what what do you what you what do you
mean I'm talking about the kind of
diplomacy that's going to end the
destruction of your country yes but if
you Mr President Mr President with
respect I think it's disrespectful for
you to come into the opal office and try
to litigate this in front of the
American Media right now you guys are
going around and forcing conscripts to
the front lines because you have
Manpower problems you should be thanking
the president for to bring an into this
conf have you ever been to Ukraine that
you say what problems we have I have
been to come once I've actually I've
actually watched and seen the stories
and I know what happens is you bring
people you bring them on a propaganda
tour Mr President are do you disagree
that you've had problems bringing people
into your military and do you think that
it's respectful to come to the Oval
Office of the United States of America
and attack the administration that is
trying to trying to prevent the destru
of your country a lot of a lot of
questions let's start from the beginning
first of all during the war everybody
has problems even you but you have nice
ocean and don't feel now but you will
feel it in the future God bless you know
God bless bless you will not have War
don't tell us what we're going to feel
we're trying to solve a problem don't
tell us what we're going to feel I'm not
telling you because you're in no
position to dictate that remember this
you're in no position to dictate what
what we're going to feel we're going to
feel very good you will feel influence
we're going to feel very good and very
strong you will feel influence you're
right now not in a very good position
you've allowed yourself to be in a very
bad position and he happens to be right
about from the very beginning of the war
you're not good position you don't have
the cards right now with us you start
having cards right now you don't you're
playing
cards you're gambling with the lives of
millions of people you're gambling with
World War I what do you think you're
gambling with World War I and what
you're doing is very dis disrespectful
to the country this
country far more than a lot of people
said they should have have you said
thank you once lot of no in this you
said thank you you went to Pennsylvania
and campaigned for the opposition in
October offer some words of appreciation
for the United States of America and the
president who's trying to save your
country
please you think that if you will speak
very loudly about the war you can he's
not speaking loudly he's not speaking
loudly your country is in big trouble
can I no no you've done a lot of talking
your country is in big trouble I know
you're not winning you're not winning
this I you have a damn good chance of
coming out okay because of us Mr
President we are staying in our country
staying strong from the very beginning
of the war we've been alone and we are
thankful I said thanks in this cabinet
not we gave you through this stupid
president $350 billion we gave you
military equipment and you men are brave
but they had to use our
military if you didn't have our military
equipment inv if you didn't have our
military equipment this war would have
been over in two weeks in three days I
heard it from Putin in three days this
is something in two weeks of course he
has it's going to be a very hard thing
to do business like this I tell you just
say thank you I said a lot
of am except that there are
disagreements and let's go litigate
those disagreements rather than trying
to fight it out in the American Media
when you're wrong we know that you're
wrong but you see I think it's good for
the American people to see what's going
on over here I think it's very important
that's why I kept this going so
long you have to be thankful you don't
have the Cs you're buried there you're
your people are dying you're running low
on soldiers listen you're running low on
solders it would be a damn good thing
and then you then you tell us I don't
want to cease fire I don't want to ceas
fire I want to go and I want to this
look if you could get a ceasefire right
now I tell you you take it so the
bullets stop Flying and you meant stop
getting killed of course we want to stop
the war but I saying you don't want to
ceas I said to you I want a ceas
guarantees because you'll get a
ceasefire faster than itre ask our
people about ceas fire what they think
that wasn't doesn't matter for you what
that wasn't with me that was with guy
named Biden who was not a smart person
that was that was with it was your
president excuse me that was with Obama
who gave you a sheets and I gave you
javelins yes I gave you the javelins to
take out all those tanks Obama gave you
sheets in fact the statement is Obama
gave sheets and Trump gave
javelins you got to be more thankful
because let me tell you you don't have
the cards with us you have the cards but
without us you don't have any cards
question to Mr Vice President sorry
going to be a tough deal to make because
the attitudes have to change what if
Russia breaks this fire what if Russia
breaks these talks what do we do then
understand that it's
a what are you saying she's asking what
if Russia breaks the ceasefire what if
they what if anything what if a bomb
drops on your head right now okay what
have they broken I don't know they broke
it with Biden because Biden they didn't
respect him they didn't respect Obama
they respect
me let me tell you Putin went through a
hell of a lot with me he went through a
phony Witch Hunt where they used him and
Russia Russia Russia Russia you ever
hear of that deal that was a phony that
was a phony Hunter Biden Joe Biden scam
Hillary Clinton Shifty Adam Schiff it
was a Democrat scam and he had to go
through that and he did go through it we
didn't end up in a war and he went
through it he was accused of all that
stuff he had nothing to do with it it
came out of Hunter Biden's bathroom it
came out of Hunter Biden's bedroom it
was disgusting and then they said oh oh
the laptop from hell was made by Russia
the 51 agents the whole thing was a scam
and he had to put up with that he was
being accused of all that stuff all I
can say is this he might have broken
deals with Obama and Bush and he might
have broken him with Biden he did maybe
maybe he didn't I don't know what
happened but he didn't break him with me
he wants to make a deal I don't know if
you can make a deal the problem is I've
empowered you to be a tough guy and I
don't think you'd be a tough guy without
the United States and your people are
very brave but you're either going to
make a deal or we're out and if we're
out you'll fight it out I don't think
it's going to be pretty but you'll fight
it out but you don't have the cards but
once we sign that deal you're in a much
better position but you're not acting at
all thankful and that's not a nice thing
I'll be honest that's not a nice thing
all right uh I think we've seen enough
what do you think huh this is this is
going to be great television I will say
that all right we'll see what we can do
about putting it together thank you
we'll
see come on
world